<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>botica on Botica</title>
    <link>https://blog.gabelula.com/es/categories/botica/</link>
    <description>Recent content in botica on Botica</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>es</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.gabelula.com/es/categories/botica/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>the next Eclectic Tech Carnival</title>
      <link>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/12/23/the-next-eclectic-tech-carnival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/12/23/the-next-eclectic-tech-carnival/</guid>
      <description>Eclectic Tech Carnival is a self-managed event around feminism and free technologies and will take
place from the 4 to the 11 Th of August in Calafou, an ecoindustrial postcapitalist colony located at 60 km from Barcelona. We will post more information in January, in the meantime save the dates!! Looking forward seeing you!
&amp;lt;www.calafou.org&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audre Lorde: “The Transformation of Silence into Language and Action”</title>
      <link>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/12/06/audre-lorde-the-transformation-of-silence-into-language-and-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/12/06/audre-lorde-the-transformation-of-silence-into-language-and-action/</guid>
      <description>“Silence will not protect you”. I love that quote. It is from an essay from Audre Lorde and it talks so much about the fear of speaking up. Is it better to hide away in a dark corner of life or go out and say what you think about injustice and oppression and your own experience?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee shops in Portland, OR where to work from</title>
      <link>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/12/06/coffee-shops-in-portland-or-where-to-work-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/12/06/coffee-shops-in-portland-or-where-to-work-from/</guid>
      <description>I love coffee shops that feel like my grandma’s living room. The ones that have very old furniture and where people share tables. The one near my house (that does not look like my grandma’s living room) that serves very good coffee is always so full of people in the mornings. Coffee shops are the social/community place for people that don’t go to churches in the US…
My favorites in the neighborhood I live in Portland,OR</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conferencia Regional de Datos Abiertos 2013 – Inscriptos por País</title>
      <link>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/12/06/conferencia-regional-de-datos-abiertos-2013-inscriptos-por-pais/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/12/06/conferencia-regional-de-datos-abiertos-2013-inscriptos-por-pais/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air and light and time and space</title>
      <link>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/09/28/air-and-light-and-time-and-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/09/28/air-and-light-and-time-and-space/</guid>
      <description>“–you know, I’ve either had a family, a job,
something has always been in the
way
but now
I’ve sold my house, I’ve found this
place, a large studio, you should see the space and
the light.
for the first time in my life I’m going to have
a place and the time to
create.”
 no baby, if you’re going to create
you’re going to create whether you work</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They plopped to the ground at my feet</title>
      <link>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/09/28/they-plopped-to-the-ground-at-my-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/09/28/they-plopped-to-the-ground-at-my-feet/</guid>
      <description>I saw my life
branching out before
me like the green
fig tree in the story
…
[The Bell Jar ]1from Silvia Plath</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adios ginebra</title>
      <link>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/09/20/adios-ginebra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/09/20/adios-ginebra/</guid>
      <description>Quiero escribir adios ginebra y encuentro la muerte como una daga obligandome a seguir. Te recuerdo. Ginebra esta impregnada de vos, de tu frances , de tus okupas, de tus letras y palabras. Tiene tu risa metida en un rincon y las noches llenas de tus pasos. Me imaginaba ginebra con las uñas pintadas de verde, azul, rojo. Imaginaba ese aire que no se como explicar. La vida esta colgada de un hilo en la plaza de saint jean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mis ciudades</title>
      <link>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/09/20/mis-ciudades/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/09/20/mis-ciudades/</guid>
      <description>Mis ciudades tienen nombres, que no son los nombres del mapa. Aquella que quedo atras tiene el color celeste de los ojos de la niña que huyo de ella. Esta, a la que llego, tiene el color de la sangre de la dictadura cuando todos empezamos a correr. La otra tiene el agridulce sabor de la pasión y su abandono. La de mas alla es un pedazo de mi corazon andando en bicicleta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moi</title>
      <link>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/09/20/moi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.gabelula.com/2013/09/20/moi/</guid>
      <description>El sueño me abomba, me emborracha. Estoy en esta caja para gallinas a nivel de halcon. Que fue lo que paso. Quien me metio en esta lata? Mi carne, mis huesos, mi sangre, mis nervios. Todo lo que he sabido de mi viaja en este cuadrado de cielo. Y alla abajo la humanidad vive sin mi.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>